http://www.hospitalityonline.com/privacy

Last updated June 29, 2019
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.hospitalityonline.com site and Hospitality Online, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Hospitality Online, Inc. include www.hospitalityonline.com and Hospitality Online. The Hospitality Online website is a hospitality job opportunities site. By using the Hospitality Online website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Hospitality Online may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, and resume. If you purchase Hospitality Online’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Hospitality Online. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Hospitality Online website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Hospitality Online’s public pages, this information may be collected and used by others.
Hospitality Online encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Hospitality Online so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Hospitality Online is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Hospitality Online website.
Use of your Personal Information
Hospitality Online collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
Hospitality Online may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Hospitality Online and its affiliates. Hospitality Online may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Hospitality Online may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Hospitality Online may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, or provide customer support. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Hospitality Online, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Hospitality Online may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Hospitality Online, in order to determine what Hospitality Online services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Hospitality Online to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Hospitality Online will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Hospitality Online or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Hospitality Online; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Hospitality Online, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Hospitality Online website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your computer by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Hospitality Online pages, or register with Hospitality Online site or services, a cookie helps Hospitality Online to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as your preferences, your resume, and so on. When you return to the same Hospitality Online website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Hospitality Online features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Hospitality Online services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Hospitality Online secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
Children Under Thirteen
Hospitality Online does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Hospitality Online by contacting us at support@hospitalityonline.com
Changes to this Statement
Hospitality Online will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Hospitality Online encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Hospitality Online is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Hospitality Online welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Hospitality Online has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Hospitality Online at:
Hospitality Online, Inc.
2601 Fourth Ave, Suite 450
Seattle, Washington 98121
Email Address: support@hospitalityonline.com
